## Supakorn Kaewjaeng

Thonburi Bangkok 10600 | +66 92-781-5935 supakorn.kaewjaeng@gmail.com | Github | LinkedIn

### **Summary**

With less than one year of real-world working experience, I was looking for a junior full-stack developer position. In my previous role, I had opportunities to contribute to high-impact commercial projects, making me learn Golang and NextJS in 2 weeks. I had opportunities to discuss, negotiate, and balance the IT and business units. I'm excited to leverage existing knowledge to accomplish the goal with teams together and gain valuable professional experiences.

#### Skill

Language: JavaScript, TypeScript, HTML, CSS, Python, Golang, SQL, Shell, Java, C++, R

Frameworks/Libraries: ReactJS, NextJS, VueJS, Playwright, Mockery, Jest, CSS(AntDesign, MaterialUI), Zustand, Redux, GORM, GIN, NestJS, NodeJS

Tools: Git, Docker, Redis, BigQuery, Jemeter, Postman, Selenium, Power BI, Tableau

Design: Figma, Adobe Illustrator (Basic), Adobe XD (Basic), AutoCAD

**Software:** SpreadSheet, Microservice, AWS Cloud Computing, Generative AI (ChatGPT, Gemini)

Other: Teamwork & Collaboration, Analytical Thinking, Communication, Fast-learner, Motivation Learner

# **Work Experience**

### **Ascend Commerce, Ascend Group**

Full Stack Software Engineer

01/2024 - Present

- Improved the internal web application base with **NextJS React Framework** which adjusted content customization to set the schedule media representation and defined content, description, and data that would be presented on the mobile application.
- Reinforced and Pushed the e-commerce platform by implementing a content management REST-API service for scheduling the content to render in a mobile application correctly using **Golang**, and ensuring precision of business logic level by **Mockery** in a **microservice architecture**.
- Optimized order service performance support at least 500k monthly transactions using a simulated load test Jmeter. Moreover, I tuned MySQL database indexing and implemented mater-slave partitioning.
- Investigated the as-is Redis in-memory cache design limitation, Designed an activity flow and added a
  new cache storage structure to eliminate limitation, and Executed new design from supervisor suggestions
- Gained an opportunity to confer and negotiate with the business unit to compromise the implemented features. Hence, Came up with design technical implementation tasks from the business scope, including UI designing, and UX leveraging in a content management service web application.

# Yannix Co., Ltd.

Frontend Software Development Engineering Intern

06/2022 - 07/2022

- Developed an end-to-end feature to support the internal organization by tracing back human resource allocation versioning estimated more than 20 users using **VueJS** and web-based **IndexedDB** storage.
- Designed UI in Figma SAS and Practiced gathering functional requirements from stakeholders with the business analyst team.
- Implement Unit Tests using **Jest**, and Manual testing, Deployed the features through the **Jenkins** web framework with the trainer.

# **Academic Project**

#### **Khunlook Nursery Web Application**

(Children's health assessment web application for large-scale enterprises)

Frontend Developer, Interviewer, UI Designer, Tester

08/2022 - 07/2023

- Developed Web Application with TypeScript React with AntDesign CSS framework and conducted UI testing with Playwright UI Automated Testing
- Launched end-to-end web application project, Interviewed and collaborated with the Khon Kaen Nurseries and the Faculty of Medicine Khon Kaen University

## JongThamTha (Entertainment web application using cloud computing technology)

Frontend developer, UI designer

03/2023 - 05/2023

- Evaluated relative efficiency and cost to extrude the maximum powerful potential of **cloud computing technology** for suitability with the project.
- Deployed frontend web application on **Amplify AWS** (AWS Cloud services).

#### **Education**

\_\_\_\_\_\_

# Chulalongkorn University B.Eng., Computer Engineering GPAX 3.62 (First class honor)

**Bangkok, Thailand** 09/2019 - 08/2023

## Certificate

# **Google Data Analytics Professional Certificate** (Coursera)

12/2023

- Examined and evaluated data from a data-centric perspective utilizing, data-driven, knowing how to handle data collection, preparation, processing, analysis, sharing, visualization, and decisions using tools such as **Google Sheets, BigQury, Tableau**, and **R**.

### **Extracurricular Activities**

\_\_\_\_\_

# Hack A Change (Thailand inequality solving design business model project)

Participant & Trainee

01/2022 - 03/2022

- Practiced business estimation and planning using Startegyzer's business model canvas template.